Now that we have put together a function that
我们已经创建了一个
will make predicted ratings for any user movie combination,
能够针对任何用户-电影组合预测评分的函数
we should try to get a better idea of how
我们应该检验下
well our predictions are matching up with the actual values that are available.
预测值与实际值之间的对比情况
Unfortunately, with everything we've done so far,
遗憾的是 到目前为止
we don't have predicted actual values that are very fair for us to judge
我们没有预测实际值供我们公平地判断效果
on because we don't have training and test splits of the data.
因为我们没有拆分出训练集和测试集
So in this notebook, we're going to do exactly that,
在此 notebook 中
we're going to split the data into training and test partitions,
我们会将数据拆分为训练集和测试集
and then we're going to see how well we can make predictions
然后看看模型对之前从未见过的
on test ratings that our model hasn't seen before.
测试评分的预测结果如何
So to do that, again we'll first read in our data set.
首先读取数据集
Once we read in the data set,
读取数据集后
we're going to create a little function that's going
我们将创建一个
to order things by a particular column,
按照特定列对数据排序的小函数
which here we just calls the order by column,
这里称之为 order_by 列
and then it's going to split our data set into a training and test set,
然后按照传入的训练大小和测试大小
determined by the training size and testing sites that we pass to it.
将数据集拆分为训练集和测试集
So, the way I'm going to do this,
我将对传入的
is I'm going to sort the reviews dataset,
reviews 数据集
which is the reviews dataset that we're going to pass in,
进行排序
and we'll sort it by just the order by column.
并按照 order_by 列排序
I'm going to store this into reviews new.
将这个存储到 reviews_new 中
Then, I'm going to make the training set,
然后将 reviews_new 的第一部分
the first part of reviews new.
当做训练集
So, a really nice way that we can do this is just to
一个比较简单的创建方法是
take a header based on the training size,
根据训练大小调用 head()
and then the validation dataset that will pass back.
然后创建验证数据集
I'll call this df, just because that's what it's called down at the bottom,
我将这个称为 df 因为下面是这么命名的
is to take the rows associated with starting at
验证集的创建方法是
the training size and then going to the training plus testing size.
从以训练大小开始的行到训练加测试大小的行
So, basically, this is going to say start at where we ended off here,
也就是从这个结束的位置开始
and then go as far as the testing size.
一直到获得测试大小
Essentially, we could do this a little differently where
也可以换一种方式
we don't pass a testing size or maybe we just go to
我们不用传入测试大小
the ending row of the reviews dataframe that's passed in.
直接到传入的 reviews dataframe 的结束行
That's another way, we could do this.
这是另一种方式
Then we can test this out by running this cell down here,
然后运行以下单元格来测试代码
which would run this function, review new.
应该会运行这个函数 review_new
Oh, and I missed,
我丢失了“s”
and that's somewhere I think reviews new, quote.
应该是 reviews_new
So then, we should have a training and testing set.
现在应该有训练集和测试集了
So, the training dataset here in this case is the 8,000,
训练集是 8,000 个评论
the testing set is 2,000,
测试集是 2,000 个评论
and then this is just the number of columns.
这是列数
Cool, and now it looks like we pass all of our tests.
不错 看来我们通过了所有测试